

#### **PROFILE**

Born in Cyprus, 21 years old computer enthusiast.

3 Years' experience in Java. 3 Years' experience in C#. 3 Years' experience in **Unity**.

Multiple Video Game Projects in Unity

and in Unreal Engine. 2 Years' experience in C++. Active person with passion in Drumming and Music.

Fluent in Greek and English, very skilled at communicating and developing

relationships in the workplace.

My goal is to work on large projects at local and/or international companies and create life-changing video games.

### CONTACT

PHONE:

+35799920132

EMAIL:

Kouis 16 cy@gmail.com

WEBSITE/PORTFOLIO:

www.nikolaskouis.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikolas-kouis-041568229/

#### **HOBBIES**

Drumming Gaming Game Development

# NIKOLAOS KOUIS

### **EDUCATION**

**Institution:** Linopetra Lyceum

Field: Physical Sciences and Computer Science

**Dates:** From 2016 to 2019

**Institution:** University of Essex

Course: BSc - Computer Science, Year 3

**Dates:** From 2020 to 2023

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## KIK Trading – Mini Mall Stores (MMS)

2021-2021

Summer job as a cashier in MMS in Limassol.

**Amdocs - Vubiquity** 

2022-2022

Software Engineering Intern.

I was working on a Web App, using JS-React and C#-.Net.

I also used **Jira** and **Azure** during my internship.

**University of Essex - Frontrunners** 

2023-

Avatar Creation – VR Developer

I am developing a VR Avatar Creation. Project "Be Yourself". Avatar Creation for Kids.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Duke of Edinburah's International Award Bronze Course
- Computer IGCSEs Mathematics IGCSEs First Language Pearson Edexcel - Second Language Cambridge
- Unity Unreal Engine Projects
- Website Designer
- The Loop: Ouroboros, Horror Game, currently on Alpha, using Unreal Enaine.
- Ritualist, Horror Game, currently on Alpha, on Unity using C#.
- Surveillance Job, published Android puzzle game, using Unity.
- Joined the Global Game Jam 2022, Horror game on Unity using C#, Finished game.
- Joined the Brackeys Game Jam 2022, Horror Shooter VR Game on Unity using C#, Finished game.
- Won the Essex Game Development Society Game Jam 2022, First Person game, using Unity.
- Joined the Amdocs Hackathon 2022, Web based Platform game, Finished game - 2<sup>nd</sup> Place.
- Joined the Global Game Jam 2023, Roque-like FPS Game, Finished game.
- Capstone Project, University Final Year Project, HomeScale VR. House Scale VR is a software that gives a more realistic experience to the user, by calculating the obstacles they have in the real world and transform them into the game.